export const QA = {
    q1: {
        question: "What is the title of Ariana Grande's debut single?",
        choices: ['Problem', 'Put Your Hearts Up', 'Bang Bang', 'The Way'],
        answer: "q1 Put Your Hearts Up",
    },
    q2: {
        question: "In which year did Ariana Grande release her first studio album?",
        choices: ['2011', '2013', '2015', '2018'],
        answer: "q2 2013"
    },
    q3: {
        question: "What is the name of Ariana Grande's fanbase?",
        choices: ['Arianators', 'Grande Army', 'Ariana\'s Angels', 'Moonlighters'],
        answer: "q3 Arianators"
    },
    q4: {
        question: "Which TV show marked Ariana Grande's acting debut?",
        choices: ["iCarly", "Victorious", "Sam & Cat", "Scream Queens"],
        answer: "q4 Victorious"
    }/* ,
    q5: {
        question: "Ariana Grande's 2019 hit song '7 Rings' is inspired by which classic musical?",
        choices: ["The Sound of Music", "My Fair Lady", "The Wizard of Oz", "The Phantom of the Opera"],
        answer: "q5 The Sound of Music"
    },
    q6: {
        question: "Which Ariana Grande album features the song 'Better Off'?",
        choices: ['Yours Truly', 'Dangerous Woman', 'Sweetener', 'Thank U, Next'],
        answer: "q6 Sweetener",
    },
    q7: {
        question: "Which song by Ariana Grande features the line \"Cause I... see right through you, boy and I, I...ain't feeling you no more I ain't feelin' you no more\"?",
        choices: ["Knew Better / Forever Boy", "No Tears Left to Cry", "One Last Time", "Greedy"],
        answer: "q7 Knew Better / Forever Boy"
    },
    q8: {
        question: "What is Ariana Grande's full name?",
        choices: ["Ariana Frankie Grande", "Ariana Butera", "Ariana Minaj", "Ariana-Butera Grande"],
        answer: "q8 Ariana Butera-Grande"
    },
    q9: {
        question: "Which Ariana Grande song features the lyrics 'I want it, I got it'?",
        choices: ['7 Rings', 'Into You', 'God is a Woman', 'Break Free'],
        answer: "q9 7 Rings",
    },
    q10: {
        question: "Which song by Ariana Grande features the line 'But this one gon' last'?",
        choices: ["Breathin", "Thank U, Next", "One Last Time", "Everyday"],
        answer: "q10 Thank U, Next"
    },
    q11: {
        question: "Which album was the name of Ariana's last tour?",
        choices: ["Thank U, Next", "Positions", "Eternal Sunshine", "Sweetener"],
        answer: "q11 Sweetener"
    },
    q12: {
        question: "Ariana has dogs, which one of these included?",
        choices: ["Merry", "Jerry", "Moore", "Toulouse"],
        answer: "q12 Toulouse"
    },
    q13: {
        question: "Which rapper has Ariana Grande collaborated the most?",
        choices: ["J. Cole", "Mac Miller", "Nicki Minaj", "Doja Cat"],
        answer: "q13 Mac Miller"
    } */
};